<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>machinemind.io</title>
        <link>https://www.machinemind.io/</link>
        <description>machinemind.io - how to work on data by siegstedt. The more data I add here, the better my Google Search results.</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>siegstedt@machinemind.io (Siegfried Eckstedt)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>siegstedt@machinemind.io (Siegfried Eckstedt)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 08:20:17 &#43;0100</lastBuildDate>
            <atom:link href="https://www.machinemind.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
        <item>
    <title>How to clone and rebuild a conda environment</title>
    <link>https://www.machinemind.io/how-to-clone-and-rebuild-conda-env/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 Mar 2021 08:20:17 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.machinemind.io/how-to-clone-and-rebuild-conda-env/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>You have created a conda environment. Good job! But you want it to be accessible to others. And, you want to recreate on a different machine. Well, here is how you can do it.</p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Git commands to live by</title>
    <link>https://www.machinemind.io/git-commands-to-live-by/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 Mar 2021 13:37:32 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.machinemind.io/git-commands-to-live-by/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Git is an essential tool for programmming. If you want to get deeper involved in coding, better be prepared to get familiar with some of the most vital commands. Here is a short summary broken down to scenarios.</p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>What tools to use for improving Python code maintenance</title>
    <link>https://www.machinemind.io/tools-to-improve-py-code/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2021 18:39:51 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.machinemind.io/tools-to-improve-py-code/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Maintenance is important. Because crafting code takes time. Therefore, your invested time should turn into a reliable product. There are some tools that can help you maintain your code base programmatically.</p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Must Read: Books for learning programming with Python</title>
    <link>https://www.machinemind.io/must-read-books-for-learning-python/</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 19:23:11 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.machinemind.io/must-read-books-for-learning-python/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Programming is an essential skill as you operate data on some machine. But, we are not all Computer Science graduate who learnt Software Engineering at uni. That&rsquo;s alright. It&rsquo;s never too late to learn a new trick. Here are some good reads to learn programming in Python.</p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to create a virtual environment with conda</title>
    <link>https://www.machinemind.io/how-to-virtual-env-with-conda/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 14:22:36 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.machinemind.io/how-to-virtual-env-with-conda/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Let&rsquo;s say you&rsquo;re working on different projects. One a nlp project. One a financial analytics projects. One a marketing analytics project.</p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to set up a secure remote workplace</title>
    <link>https://www.machinemind.io/how-to-setup-secure-remote-workplace/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jan 2021 16:15:51 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.machinemind.io/how-to-setup-secure-remote-workplace/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>You listen to the sound of the waves craching into the shore. You feel the sand under your bare feet. A dream of a remote work place. Though, is it secure? And if there was a secure remote work place, how can I set it up on my machine?</p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>How to set up a webpage using HUGO, Netlify, and Git</title>
    <link>https://www.machinemind.io/how-to-set-up-hugo-and-netlify/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2021 12:29:51 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.machinemind.io/how-to-set-up-hugo-and-netlify/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>This is my <strong>first time</strong> using a static website builder. So far, I have used to built pages with WordPress. But I have never truly made friends with the UI and got a confused too easily with the many additional plugins it required to get up something nice.</p>
<p>So, as a I thought about setting up a new site, I followed the recommendation of a friend to check out Hugo. The promise of a simple to use and shiny new open-source tool got hooked up. And so I&rsquo;m sitting here and start with <strong>Hugo, Netlify and Git</strong>.</p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Must Watch: Good AI channels on Youtube</title>
    <link>https://www.machinemind.io/must-watch-ai-channels-on-youtube/</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 15:56:38 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.machinemind.io/must-watch-ai-channels-on-youtube/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>I guess, I just really like watching YouTube. And because of my recent endeavors in Data Science, I came across some channels that got my neurons fired. Lacking of a better title, I simply present must watch list of &ldquo;Good AI channels on YouTube&rdquo;.</p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Must Watch: Youtube channels for learning Data Science</title>
    <link>https://www.machinemind.io/must-watch-youtube-channels-for-learning-data-science/</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jan 2020 20:51:19 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.machinemind.io/must-watch-youtube-channels-for-learning-data-science/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>Is there some good content on YouTube to learn about Data Science? Sure thing, yes! YoutTube is a tremendous source of content of all kinds - and so it is for Data Science. Here is a short list of YouTube channels I found enjoyable to learn on topics and be inspired to try out new stuff.</p>]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Must Read: Books for learning Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence</title>
    <link>https://www.machinemind.io/must-read-books-for-learning-ml-ai/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 04:31:13 &#43;0100</pubDate>
    <author>Author</author>
    <guid>https://www.machinemind.io/must-read-books-for-learning-ml-ai/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<p>What are your favorite books on Machine Learning or Artificial Intelligence? In the series of must read books, I feature theme-specific lists of books on various topics. Here is the start of the series covering the theme Machine Learning and Artificial Intelligence. On purpose, it&rsquo;s a fairly condensed list of six books. So I trust that you have a few suggestions what piece could make a good addition.</p>]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
